Finding Aid for General Motors Corporation. Public Relations Department records, 1941-1955
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
General Motors Corporation. Public Relations Department records 1941-1955
General Motors Corporation. Dept. of Public Relations.
4 linear feet
88309 Bb 2
Minutes of the Public Relations Planning Committee, and of the Public Relations Policy Committee; also manual, 1955, of the Manpower Planning Program.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The record group was donated by David E. Lewis (donor no. 4999 ), professor of business history at the University of Michigan in November 1986.
Periodic additions to the records are not expected.
The record group is open to research.
The Department of Public Relations is one of the divisions of the General Motors Corporation.
The General Motors Department of Public Relations record group has been divided into three series: the Public Relations Planning Committee, Public Relations Policy Committee, and the Manpower Planning Program. In addition to original material, a negative microfilm is also available.
Subjects:
General Motors Corporation. Dept. of Public Relations.; Automobile industry and trade--United States.
- Public Relations Planning Committee meeting minutes, (bound volumes
  The Public Relations Planning Committee consists of minutes of meetings 1942 to 1952, all contained in bound volumes.
  - 1942-1943 (Box 1)
  - 1944 (Box 1)
  - 1945 (Box 1)
  - 1946 (Box 1)
  - 1947-1948 (Box 1)
  - 1949 (Box 1)
  - 1950 (Box 2)
  - 1951 (Box 2)
  - 1952 (Box 2)
- Public Relations Policy Committee meeting minutes
  The Public Relations Policy Committee consists of minutes of meetings 1941 to 1952, all contained in bound volumes.
  - 1941-1943 (Box 2)
  - 1944 (Box 2)
  - 1945 (Box 3)
  - 1946 (Box 3)
  - 1947-1948 (Box 3)
  - March 23,1949 (Box 4)
  - May 18, 1949 (Box 4)
  - September 21, 1949 (Box 4)
  - October 19, 1949 (Box 4)
  - November 16, 1949 (Box 4)
  - February 22, 1950 (Box 4)
  - June 21, 1950 (Box 4)
  - October 17, 1950 (Box 4)
  - November 14, 1950 (Box 4)
  - April 17, 1951 (Box 4)
  - May 22, 1951 (Box 4)
  - September 18, 1951 (Box 4)
  - April 22, 1952 (Box 4)
- Manpower Planning Program
  - Manual, March, 1955 (Box 4)